<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<filename>ProtectorCaption_dlc01.fmg</filename>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="3000000">The sun-faded and lightly soiled hat of Dryleaf Dane. Worn low over the eyes, it obscures the wearer's vision.

Meeting the gaze of another can overcome the senses, often leading to the downfall of those who would walk the noble and solitary seekers' path.</text>
<text id="3000100">Sun-faded and lightly soiled travel attire worn by clergymen.

The gold necklace found under the breast belongs to a group of spiritual seekers known as the Dryleaf Sect.

This sect rejects dependence on others in all matters of faith, seeking self-discipline and self-sufficiency above all else.</text>
<text id="3000200">Sun-faded and lightly soiled arm wraps.

Wound tightly around the arms as if it might prevent them from being broken.</text>
<text id="3000300">Sun-faded and lightly soiled travel attire worn by clergymen.
Boots made of sturdy leather.</text>
<text id="3001100">Sun-faded and lightly soiled travel attire worn by clergymen.

The leather satchel hanging from the shoulder is decorated with one of Miquella's emblems, a golden grass motif.</text>
<text id="3010000">The black iron helm of Commander Gaius.
Part of an armor set patterned after fallen seeds.

Gaius was the most senior disciple of the same Alabaster Lord who taught Radahn and Gaea gravitational technique.</text>
<text id="3010100">The black iron chest armor of Commander Gaius.
Part of an armor set patterned after fallen seeds.

Gaius was the most senior disciple of the same Alabaster Lord who taught Radahn and Gaea gravitational technique.</text>
<text id="3010200">The black iron gauntlets of Commander Gaius.
Part of an armor set patterned after fallen seeds.

Gaius was the most senior disciple of the same Alabaster Lord who taught Radahn and Gaea gravitational technique.</text>
<text id="3010300">Black iron greaves made for Commander Gaius.
A cruel joke, for he could not wear them.

Riding atop the boar he called his other half, Gaius was in fact a warrior of albinauric extraction.</text>
<text id="5000000">An Oathseeker Knight helm.
Black with gold ornamentation.

These knights set off on quests of discovery, hoping to find by themselves an oath of their own choosing to serve in perfect, lifelong devotion.</text>
<text id="5000100">Chest armor of Needle Knight Leda.

Slightly strengthens attacks following a dodge roll or backstep, as well as dash attacks.

Embroidered with a golden crossed-tree motif, the chalk white cloak and surcoat symbolize the honor of the Needle Knights.

"Kindly Miquella fashioned us as his needles to quell all, to ward away all."</text>
<text id="5000200">Oathseeker Knight gauntlets.
Black with gold ornamentation.

These knights set off on quests of discovery, hoping to find by themselves an oath of their own choosing to serve in perfect, lifelong devotion.</text>
<text id="5000300">Oathseeker Knight greaves.
Black with gold ornamentation.

These knights set off on quests of discovery, hoping to find by themselves an oath of their own choosing to serve in perfect, lifelong devotion.</text>
<text id="5002100">Oathseeker Knight chest armor.
Black with gold ornamentation.

These knights set off on quests of discovery, hoping to find by themselves an oath of their own choosing to serve in perfect, lifelong devotion.</text>
<text id="5010000">Helm made from an unusual metal known as verdigris.

Verdigris is said to be the gift of an outer god.
Possessed of an enormously hefty yet supple strength thanks to its rusted nature.</text>
<text id="5010100">Chest armor made from an unusual metal known as verdigris.

Verdigris is said to be the gift of an outer god.
Possessed of an enormously hefty yet supple strength thanks to its rusted nature.</text>
<text id="5010200">Gauntlets made from an unusual metal known as verdigris.

Verdigris is said to be the gift of an outer god.
Possessed of an enormously hefty yet supple strength thanks to its rusted nature.</text>
<text id="5010300">Greaves made from an unusual metal known as verdigris.

Verdigris is said to be the gift of an outer god.
Possessed of an enormously hefty yet supple strength thanks to its rusted nature.</text>
<text id="5020000">The pelt of Ralva the Great Red Bear, worn upon the head without modification.

Enhances incantations of what is jokingly called "Bear Communion."

This untreated hide, won at the end of a bloody bout, is just the thing to make a wild bear out of a warrior.</text>
<text id="5020100">Chest armor of Red Bear, whose name is lost to madness.
A vest reinforced with iron rivets.

After killing the great red bear in a blood-soaked bout, he became fascinated by the untainted glory of its naked strength.

"I wish to be a bear, no more, and no less."</text>
<text id="5020200">Gauntlets of Red Bear, whose name is lost to madness.
Reinforced with iron rivets.

After killing the great red bear in a blood-soaked bout, he became fascinated by the untainted glory of its naked strength.

"I wish to be a bear, no more, and no less."</text>
<text id="5020300">Greaves of Red Bear, whose name is lost to madness.
Reinforced with iron rivets.

After killing the great red bear in a blood-soaked bout, he became fascinated by the untainted glory of its naked strength.

"I wish to be a bear, no more, and no less."</text>
<text id="5021000">Helm of Red Bear, whose name is lost to madness.
The cheek guards are shaped after lion fangs.

Perhaps his fascination with the untamed strength of the wild stemmed from his past as a Redmane.</text>
<text id="5030000">A mask upon which is carved a tranquil sleeping face.

The silver hair is arranged in the same style as St. Trina's, increasing arcane.

Just once, Thiollier was granted the sweet repose of velvety sleep. The remainder of his days would be spent attempting to recapture it.</text>
<text id="5030100">The dark attire of those who wield poison in secret.

The silver hair is arranged in the same style as St. Trina's, increasing arcane.

Additionally, countless needles are sewn onto the exterior, apparently for talismanic effect.</text>
<text id="5030200">The dark gloves of those who wield poison in secret, ever scorned and loathed.</text>
<text id="5030300">The dark trousers of those who wield poison in secret, ever scorned and loathed.</text>
<text id="5031100">The dark attire of those who wield poison in secret.

Countless needles are sewn onto the exterior for talismanic effect.</text>
<text id="5060000">The hat of Count Ymir, High Priest.

The circular design at the top represents the Greater Will and its lightless abyss, imparting increased intelligence and arcane to the wearer.

Though Count Ymir instructed Rellana in the sorcerous arts, he abandoned his allegiance to the moon.

"It was merely the closest of the celestial bodies. Nothing more."</text>
<text id="5060100">Robe of Count Ymir, High Priest.
Conceals the abundance of squirming beneath.

Gold embroidery decorates the purple cloth, with a jewelled ruff that sparkles like a flower wet with dew.</text>
<text id="5060200">Gloves of Count Ymir, High Priest.
Soft and well-tailored.</text>
<text id="5060300">Undergarments of Count Ymir, High Priest.
Soft and well-tailored.</text>
<text id="5062100">Robe of Count Ymir, High Priest.
The front is open, exposing the squirming fingers beneath.

This robe is the image of his fervent desire having broken free, laying bare his greatest wish, and wearing it enhances finger sorceries.

"I will be the true mother.
My fingers will grant us redemption!"</text>
<text id="5070000">Grotesque mask constructed from countless solidified caterpillars. A ritual implement of the greater potentates of Bonny Village.

Used to ward off thoughts of impurity, doubt, temptation, and other wickednesses one is vulnerable to while absorbed in divine ritual.</text>
<text id="5070100">Ragged black cloth overlaid with braided cord. Attire of a vengeance-seeking hornsent.

The braided cord ties together the vow of the revenger with the victims' grudges. It must never come undone.

Enhances both watchful spirits and the vengeful spirits summoned by horned bairns.</text>
<text id="5070200">Ragged black cloth tied with braided cord. Attire of a vengeance-seeking hornsent.</text>
<text id="5070300">This lightly soiled loincloth of ragged cloth does little more than conceal one's nether regions.</text>
<text id="5080000">Bright-red hood of the Ranah dancers.
Enhances the power of dancing attacks.

The dance of Ranah is one of burning passion, and the most passionate dancers never allow their fiery dance to end, losing even their names as they dance on.

To see the passion fade is to see the dancer's flame extinguished.</text>
<text id="5080100">Bright-red dress of the Ranah dancers.
Enhances the power of dancing attacks.

The dance of Ranah is one of burning passion, and the most passionate dancers never allow their fiery dance to end, losing even their names as they dance on.

To see the passion fade is to see the dancer's flame extinguished.</text>
<text id="5080200">Metal bracer of the Ranah dancers.

Enhances the power of dancing attacks.

Designed to protect the sword-wielding hand.</text>
<text id="5080300">Long, black trousers worn underneath the deep crimson dress of the Ranah dancers.

Enhances the power of dancing attacks.</text>
<text id="5081100">Altered form of the deep crimson dress of the Ranah dancers.
These are the black undergarments worn beneath.

Enhances the power of dancing attacks.</text>
<text id="5090000">Bottomless black helm, cool to the touch.
Flowing lines in the seeming shape of a fingerprint adorn the surface. Imprisons the wearer in utterly lightless dark.

Bestowed upon those born deep underground, ordaining them as Swordhands of Night.</text>
<text id="5090100">Bottomless black chest armor, cool to the touch.
Flowing lines in the seeming shape of a fingerprint adorn the surface. Imprisons the wearer in utterly lightless dark.

Bestowed upon those born deep underground, ordaining them as Swordhands of Night.</text>
<text id="5090200">Bottomless black gauntlets, cool to the touch.
Flowing lines in the seeming shape of a fingerprint adorn the surface. Imprisons the wearer in utterly lightless dark.

Bestowed upon those born deep underground, ordaining them as Swordhands of Night.</text>
<text id="5090300">Bottomless greaves, cool to the touch.
Flowing lines in the seeming shape of a fingerprint adorn the surface. Imprisons the wearer in utterly lightless dark.

Bestowed upon those born deep underground, ordaining them as Swordhands of Night.</text>
<text id="5100000">Helm of the broken drake warrior Igon, from a set of armor comprised of a miscellany of parts. This tattered protective-wear is shaped like a bugle.

The poor scavenger of battlefields found honor through Dragon Communion.</text>
<text id="5100100">Armor of the broken drake warrior Igon, from a set comprised of a miscellany of parts. Filthy belongings are attached to this tattered piece of protective-wear.

The poor scavenger of battlefields found honor through Dragon Communion.</text>
<text id="5100200">Gauntlets of the broken drake warrior Igon. 
No more than a mish-mash of tatters and remnants stripped from a corpse found in the aftermath of a battle.</text>
<text id="5100300">Loincloth of the broken drake warrior Igon. Stripped from a corpse found in the aftermath of a battle, this scrap of cloth smells utterly foul.</text>
<text id="5101000">Helm of the broken drake warrior Igon, from a set of armor comprised of a miscellany of parts. Patched with scraps of cloth.

The poor scavenger of battlefields found honor through Dragon Communion.</text>
<text id="5101100">Armor of the broken drake warrior Igon, from a set comprised of a miscellany of parts. Patched with scraps of cloth.

The poor scavenger of battlefields found honor through Dragon Communion.</text>
<text id="5110000">The iron mask of Sir Ansbach, giving the appearance of a quiet, wise, old bearded man.

But an old fear lurks beneath, together with the cold, unflinching discipline that once honed his blade, now employed to enhance Blood Oath and dynastic skills.</text>
<text id="5110100">Attire of Sir Ansbach. The embroidered crest of the Pureblood Knights has now all but faded away.

Slightly enhances Blood Oath and dynastic skills.

Ansbach understood that keeping his oath to his old master was not an act of logic, nor would it bear any justice, but it was for these very reasons he was unable to let go.</text>
<text id="5110200">Manchettes of Sir Ansbach. Black leather adorned with gold embroidery.

Slightly enhances Blood Oath and dynastic skills.</text>
<text id="5110300">Boots of Sir Ansbach. Black leather adorned with gold embroidery.

Slightly enhances Blood Oath and dynastic skills.</text>
<text id="5111100">Attire of Sir Ansbach. Black cloth adorned with gold embroidery.

Slightly enhances Blood Oath and dynastic skills.</text>
<text id="5120000">Golden helm of Redmane Freyja, member of General Radahn's most distinguished knights.

A hideous scarlet wound was once hewn into the center of her face.

Later, Miquella gently put his lips to it and the unfading scar became the compass that Freyja would thereafter follow.</text>
<text id="5120100">Golden armor of Redmane Freyja, member of General Radahn's most distinguished knights. Affixed with a black woolen mantle.

After witnessing Freyja's valor as a gladiator in his youth, Radahn invited her to join the ranks of his most trusted warriors.</text>
<text id="5120200">Golden gauntlets of Redmane Freyja, member of General Radahn's most distinguished knights.

After witnessing Freyja's valor as a gladiator in his youth, Radahn invited her to join the ranks of his most trusted warriors.</text>
<text id="5120300">Greaves of Redmane Freyja, member of General Radahn's most distinguished knights.

After witnessing Freyja's valor as a gladiator in his youth, Radahn invited her to join the ranks of his most trusted warriors.</text>
<text id="5121100">Golden armor of Redmane Freyja, member of General Radahn's most distinguished knights.

After witnessing Freyja's valor as a gladiator in his youth, Radahn invited her to join the ranks of his most trusted warriors.</text>
<text id="5130000">Steel helm of the Knights of the Solitary Gaol.
Part of a heavy armor set that covers the whole body in overlapping plates of steel.

The nameless mausoleums of the realm of shadow are said to hold the spirits of warriors who lost their names, or their hearts.</text>
<text id="5130100">Steel chest armor of the Knights of the Solitary Gaol.
Part of a heavy armor set that covers the whole body in overlapping plates of steel, and bedecked with a black cloak.

The nameless mausoleums of the realm of shadow are said to hold the spirits of warriors who lost their names, or their hearts.</text>
<text id="5130200">Steel gauntlets of the Knights of the Solitary Gaol.
Part of a heavy armor set that covers the whole body in overlapping plates of steel.

The nameless mausoleums of the realm of shadow are said to hold the spirits of warriors who lost their names, or their hearts.</text>
<text id="5130300">Steel greaves of the Knights of the Solitary Gaol.
Part of a heavy armor set that covers the whole body in overlapping plates of steel.

The nameless mausoleums of the realm of shadow are said to hold the spirits of warriors who lost their names, or their hearts.</text>
<text id="5131100">Steel chest armor of the Knights of the Solitary Gaol.
Part of a heavy armor set that covers the whole body in overlapping plates of steel.

The nameless mausoleums of the realm of shadow are said to hold the spirits of warriors who lost their names, or their hearts.</text>
<text id="5140000">Helm worn by soldiers who serve Messmer the Impaler. The iron helm features a visor.

Though the engraving upon the forehead is a Scadutree design, it is etched in gold. A small consolation to those forced to wage a war without grace or honor.</text>
<text id="5140100">Armor worn by soldiers who serve Messmer the Impaler. A ragged cloak is draped over rusted mail.

Though the chestpiece features a Scadutree motif, gold has been used for its engraving. A small consolation to those forced to wage a war without grace or honor.</text>
<text id="5140200">Gauntlets worn by soldiers who serve Messmer the Impaler, rusted and crusted in filth from fighting in unending war.</text>
<text id="5140300">Greaves worn by soldiers who serve Messmer the Impaler, rusted and crusted in filth from fighting in unending war.</text>
<text id="5141100">Armor worn by soldiers who serve Messmer the Impaler. The mail has rusted while fighting in unending war.

Though the chestpiece features a Scadutree motif, gold has been used for its engraving. A small consolation to those forced to wage a war without grace or honor.</text>
<text id="5150000">Helm worn by the Black Knights, servants of Messmer the Impaler. Black iron ornamented with gold. A rotten odor stubbornly clings to it.

Perhaps it arises from the tainted nature of the blood that splattered upon it. Or perhaps it is the wearer's own blackened soul, festering after endless slaughter.</text>
<text id="5150100">Armor worn by the Black Knights, servants of Messmer the Impaler.

Though the engraving above the heart is a Scadutree design, it is etched in gold. A small consolation to those forced to wage a war without grace or honor.</text>
<text id="5150200">Gauntlets worn by the Black Knights, servants of Messmer the Impaler. Black iron ornamented with gold. A rotten odor stubbornly clings to it.

Perhaps it arises from the tainted nature of the blood that splattered upon it. Or perhaps it is the wearer's own blackened soul, festering after endless slaughter.</text>
<text id="5150300">Greaves worn by the Black Knights, servants of Messmer the Impaler. Black iron ornamented with gold. A rotten odor stubbornly clings to it.

Perhaps it arises from the tainted nature of the blood that splattered upon it. Or perhaps it is the wearer's own blackened soul, festering after endless slaughter.</text>
<text id="5160000">Helm of Rakshasa, soaked in the spurting blood of her victims. Tatters of ragged cloth jut out haphazardly, as if her lust for carnage threatens to break free.

Increases damage dealt to foes, but greatly increases damage taken by the wearer.

Cut down and devour. Only those who repeat the cycle without rest can truly subvert the self and become Rakshasa.</text>
<text id="5160100">Armor of Rakshasa, soaked in the spurting blood of her victims. Tatters of ragged cloth jut out haphazardly, as if her lust for carnage threatens to break free.

Increases damage dealt to foes, but greatly increases damage taken by the wearer.

Cut down and devour. Only those who repeat the cycle without rest can truly subvert the self and become Rakshasa.</text>
<text id="5160200">Gauntlets of Rakshasa, soaked in the spurting blood of her victims. Tatters of ragged cloth jut out haphazardly, as if her lust for carnage threatens to break free.

Increases damage dealt to foes, but greatly increases damage taken by the wearer.

Cut down and devour. Only those who repeat the cycle without rest can truly subvert the self and become Rakshasa.</text>
<text id="5160300">Greaves of Rakshasa, soaked the spurting blood of her victims. Tatters of ragged cloth jut out haphazardly, as if her lust for carnage threatens to break free.

Increases damage dealt to foes, but greatly increases damage taken by the wearer.

Cut down and devour. Only those who repeat the cycle without rest can truly subvert the self and become Rakshasa.</text>
<text id="5180000">Pointed helm of the Fire Knights under Messmer the Impaler's personal command.

Slightly increases maximum HP, stamina, and maximum equip load.

Each and every knight hailed from a renowned family of the Erdtree's upper echelons, but were shunned and chased from their homes after pledging allegiance to Messmer as their master.</text>
<text id="5180100">Armor of the Fire Knights under Messmer the Impaler's personal command.

Distinguished by its red cape and twin golden snakes which adorn the neck, enhancing incantations of Messmer's flame.

These were the only ones who truly knew Messmer. His flames, like serpents. The painful fate that accompanied his accursed form.</text>
<text id="5180200">Gauntlets of the Fire Knights under Messmer the Impaler's personal command.

Each and every knight hailed from a renowned family of the Erdtree's upper echelons, but were shunned and chased from their homes after pledging allegiance to Messmer as their master.</text>
<text id="5180300">Greaves of the Fire Knights under Messmer the Impaler's personal command.

Each and every knight hailed from a renowned family of the Erdtree's upper echelons, but were shunned and chased from their homes after pledging allegiance to Messmer as their master.</text>
<text id="5181100">Armor of the Fire Knights under Messmer the Impaler's personal command.

Each and every knight hailed from a renowned family of the Erdtree's upper echelons, but were shunned and chased from their homes after pledging allegiance to Messmer as their master.</text>
<text id="5182000">Helm of Wego, elder among the Fire Knights. Two warped death masks stacked one atop the other.

Reduces FP used to summon spirits.

Gnawed at by loneliness, the old man turned his attention to the spirituality of Messmer's flame, using it in a rite of resurrection.

Yet the soulless bodies he brought to life were no comfort to poor Wego.</text>
<text id="5183000">Helm of Kood, captain of the Fire Knights. A winged serpent perches atop it.

Enhances Fire Knight skills.

The winged serpent is the token creature of Messmer's military forces. It is a wise friend which keeps the base serpent at bay and holds its power in check.</text>
<text id="5184000">Hood of Salza, sage of the Fire Knights.

A prodigious amount of cloth wound around it, giving the impression of a greatly swollen head, and wearing it increases intelligence.

A disciple of the elder Wego, he refused to burn down an old ruin, at the risk of his own life.</text>
<text id="5190000">Headband worn by highland warriors, made of woven leather. The white favor represents their home settlement.

Highland warriors are known to be hunters of bears; to them, there is no act more glorious than the subjugation of a savage beast.</text>
<text id="5190100">Traditional garb of highland warriors, made from woven fabric and finished with fur. This garment is made from fabrics with both blue and red patterns.

Red-patterned fabrics were allowed only to those who hunted bears—the greatest and most glorious of the highlanders.</text>
<text id="5190200">Arm wraps worn by highland warriors, made of sturdy leather and fastened with winding straps.

Highland warriors are known to be hunters of bears; to them, there is no act more glorious than the subjugation of a savage beast.</text>
<text id="5190300">Leg wraps worn by highland warriors, made of sturdy leather and fastened with winding straps. The addition of animal pelt keeps the wearer warm.

Highland warriors are known to be hunters of bears; to them, there is no act more glorious than the subjugation of a savage beast.</text>
<text id="5191000">Helm worn by highland warriors, pieced together using leather. The white favor represents their home settlement.

Highland warriors are known to be hunters of bears; to them, there is no act more glorious than the subjugation of a savage beast.</text>
<text id="5191100">Traditional garb of highland warriors, made from woven fabric and finished with a blue patterned cloth.

Highland warriors are known to be hunters of bears; to them, there is no act more glorious than the subjugation of a savage beast.</text>
<text id="5200000">Golden helm of the Death Knights, whose own death masks served as the visards of their armor.

Enhances skills and incantations of the capital's ancient dragon cult.

The decayed golden wheel that adorns it represents their unbroken loyalty to Godwyn, he who became Prince of Death.</text>
<text id="5200100">Golden armor of the Death Knights, adorned with an antiquated depiction of the Erdtree.

Enhances skills and incantations of the capital's ancient dragon cult.

These knights, once Godwyn's personal guard, quested to find their transfigured master's cadaver surrogate—for the coming age of the Duskborn.</text>
<text id="5200200">Golden gauntlets of the Death Knights, adorned with an antiquated depiction of the Erdtree.

Enhances skills and incantations of the capital's ancient dragon cult.

These knights, once Godwyn's personal guard, quested to find their transfigured master's cadaver surrogate—for the coming age of the Duskborn.</text>
<text id="5200300">Golden greaves of the Death Knights, adorned with an antiquated depiction of the Erdtree.

Enhances skills and incantations of the capital's ancient dragon cult.

These knights, once Godwyn's personal guard, quested to find their transfigured master's cadaver surrogate—for the coming age of the Duskborn.</text>
<text id="5210000">A mask affixed with a crown of tangled horns, worn by those who would invoke divinity.

Divine invocation heightens the dexterity of the wearer, but causes the blessing of the Erdtree to become nauseating, reducing the restorative effect of drinking from a flask of sacred tears.

Focus is also troubled by wearing this mask.</text>
<text id="5210100">Attire of the tower's ascetics, embodying their commitment to an austere existence of strict self-control.

In order to ascend from their mortal flesh into tutelary deities of the land, they heighten their spirituality through severe ascetic training.</text>
<text id="5210200">Wrist guards of the tower's ascetics which embody their commitment to an austere existence of strict self-control.

In order to ascend from their mortal flesh into tutelary deities of the land, they heighten their spirituality through severe ascetic training.</text>
<text id="5210300">Ankle guards of the tower's ascetics which embody their commitment to an austere existence of strict self-control.

In order to ascend from their mortal flesh into tutelary deities of the land, they heighten their spirituality through severe ascetic training.</text>
<text id="5220000">Black helm of Messmer the Impaler, crowned with two intertwined winged serpents.
Slightly enhances incantations of Messmer's flame as well as Fire Knight skills.

The winged snakes were Messmer's constant companions.

They were there when the base serpent was sealed away behind his eye. They were there through his eternity of suffering. They will accompany him yet, in his hideous new form born when he destroyed the grace granted by his mother. They have accepted his fate as much as he.</text>
<text id="5220100">Black armor of Messmer the Impaler.
Draped with a red cloak bearing his crest embroidered.

On his mother's wishes, Messmer made himself a symbol of fear, undertaking the cleansing crusade she desired.

"Direct thy maledictions, thine ire, and thy grief towards me alone."</text>
<text id="5220200">Black gauntlets of Messmer the Impaler.

On his mother's wishes, Messmer made himself a symbol of fear, undertaking the cleansing crusade she desired.

"Direct thy maledictions, thine ire, and thy grief towards me alone."</text>
<text id="5220300">Black greaves of Messmer the Impaler.

On his mother's wishes, Messmer made himself a symbol of fear, undertaking the cleansing crusade she desired.

"Direct thy maledictions, thine ire, and thy grief towards me alone."</text>
<text id="5221000">Black helm of Messmer the Impaler, crowned with two intertwined winged serpents. Slightly enhances incantations of Messmer's fire as well as Fire Knight skills.

The winged snakes were Messmer's constant companions.

They were there when the base serpent was sealed away behind his eye. They were there through his eternity of suffering. They will accompany him yet, in his hideous new form born when he destroyed the grace granted by his mother. They have accepted his fate as much as he.</text>
<text id="5230000">Stone helm with a tinge of green. One of a set of armor pieces cast in the image of the Gravebird.
Empowers spells which summon rings of spectral light.

Gravebirds are ancient golems, created to guard the spiritgraves built where all manners of Death ultimately drift.</text>
<text id="5230100">Stone armor with a tinge of green. One of a set of armor pieces cast in the image of the Gravebird.
Featuring a cape of black Deathbird feathers, it enhances jumping attacks.

Gravebirds are ancient golems, created to guard the spiritgraves built where all manners of Death ultimately drift.</text>
<text id="5230200">Stone bracelets with a tinge of green. One of a set of armor pieces cast in the image of the Gravebird.

Gravebirds are ancient golems, created to guard the spiritgraves built where all manners of Death ultimately drift.</text>
<text id="5230300">Stone anklets with a tinge of green. One of a set of armor pieces cast in the image of the Gravebird.

Gravebirds are ancient golems, created to guard the spiritgraves built where all manners of Death ultimately drift.</text>
<text id="5231100">Stone armor with a tinge of green. One of a set of armor pieces cast in the image of the Gravebird.

Gravebirds are ancient golems, created to guard the spiritgraves built where all manners of Death ultimately drift.</text>
<text id="5240000">Helm of the rank-and-file soldiers of Messmer's army.

A pitch-dark soot clings to it, much like the inner faces of the men who wore them.</text>
<text id="5240100">Cloth armor of the rank-and-file soldiers of Messmer's army.

A pitch-dark soot clings to it, much like the inner faces of the men who wore them.</text>
<text id="5240200">Gauntlets of the rank-and-file soldiers of Messmer's army.

A pitch-dark soot clings to it, much like the inner faces of the men who wore them.</text>
<text id="5240300">Greaves of the rank-and-file soldiers of Messmer's army.

A pitch-dark soot clings to it, much like the inner faces of the men who wore them.</text>
<text id="5250000">Helm featuring a crown of sturdy tangled horns, allowing the wearer to invoke divinity. Attire of the horned warriors, keepers of the tower.

Divine invocation bolsters the strength of the wearer, but causes the blessing of the Erdtree to become nauseating, reducing the restorative effect of drinking from a flask of sacred tears.

Focus is also troubled by wearing this helm.</text>
<text id="5250100">Armor of the horned warriors, keepers of the tower.

The ochre fabric is draped over a chest-piece made to resemble the unclothed form of a hero from older times.</text>
<text id="5250200">Gauntlets of the horned warriors, keepers of the tower, made from a thick metal.</text>
<text id="5250300">Greaves of the horned warriors, keepers of the tower. Shaped to resemble the unclothed form of a hero from older times.</text>
<text id="5252000">A helm of tangled horn attached to a divine beast mask, allowing the wearer to invoke divinity. Worn by divine beast warriors; the chosen of the horned warriors.

Divine invocation heightens intensity of the storm alongside strength and dexterity, but reduces the restorative effect of drinking from a flask of sacred tears.

Focus is also troubled by wearing this helm.</text>
<text id="5252100">Armor of feted horned warriors chosen to become divine beast warriors, adorned with a lion's pelt.

Among the divine beast warriors, only those who truly excel at divine invocation become sculpted keepers, and are granted the honor of the lion dance.</text>
<text id="5253000">A helm of tangled horn attached to a divine bird mask, allowing the wearer to invoke divinity. Worn by divine bird warriors; the very first of all horned warriors.

Divine invocation heightens the power of divine bird feathers alongside strength and dexterity, but reduces the restorative effect of drinking from a flask of sacred tears.

Focus is also troubled by wearing this helm.</text>
<text id="5253100">Armor of divine bird warriors, the very first of all horned warriors, made from a golden metal.

The golden-hued divine birds are known to be cruel, never taking to human companionship. Those who invoked their divinity were few and far between.</text>
<text id="5253200">Gauntlets of divine bird warriors, the very first of all horned warriors, made from a golden metal.

The golden-hued divine birds are known to be cruel, never taking to human companionship. Those who invoked their divinity were few and far between.</text>
<text id="5253300">Greaves of divine bird warriors, the very first of all horned warriors, made from a golden metal.

The great, sharp talons increase the force generated by kicks.</text>
<text id="5260000">Ornate helm of Rellana, the Twin Moon Knight, fashioned from silver steel.

Rennala, head of the royal family of Caria, was said to have given her younger sister, who renounced her lineage to chase after Messmer, a gift of lustrous black hair.</text>
<text id="5260100">Ornate armor of Rellana, the Twin Moon Knight, fashioned from silver steel.

Adorned with the lapis-lazuli blue that is symbolic of Caria, its radiance is yet to fully fade.</text>
<text id="5260200">Gloves of Rellana, the Twin Moon Knight, fashioned from quality leather.</text>
<text id="5260300">Ornate greaves of Rellana, the Twin Moon Knight, fashioned from silver steel.</text>
<text id="5270000">The golden helm worn by Radahn in his younger years. Proudly displaying his heroic red hair, it is fitting attire for a lion.

When Malenia, Blade of Miquella, let the rotflower blossom in Aeonia, Radahn heard a murmur in his ear—

"Miquella awaits thee, O promised consort."</text>
<text id="5270100">The golden armor worn by Radahn in his younger years. Proudly adorned with heroic red accents, it is fitting attire for a lion.

When Malenia, Blade of Miquella, let the rotflower blossom in Aeonia, Radahn heard a murmur in his ear—

"Miquella awaits thee, O promised consort."</text>
<text id="5270200">The golden gauntlets worn by Radahn in his younger years.

When Malenia, Blade of Miquella, let the rotflower blossom in Aeonia, Radahn heard a murmur in his ear—

"Miquella awaits thee, O promised consort."</text>
<text id="5270300">The golden greaves worn by Radahn in his younger years. Worn by a fierce lion.

When Malenia, Blade of Miquella, let the rotflower blossom in Aeonia, Radahn heard a murmur in his ear—

"Miquella awaits thee, O promised consort."</text>
<text id="5271100">The golden armor worn by Radahn in his younger years. Worn by a fierce lion.

When Malenia, Blade of Miquella, let the rotflower blossom in Aeonia, Radahn heard a murmur in his ear—

"Miquella awaits thee, O promised consort."</text>
<text id="5272000">The circlet of light which adorned Miquella's head as he returned in divine aspect. It has begun to fade into nothingness.

Slightly boosts intelligence, faith, and arcane, while also boosting the power of Miquella's light.

This circle was to be the very foundation upon which Miquella's age of compassion would be built, should it have ever come to pass.</text>
<text id="5280000">Helm as dark as shadow, worn by vulgar militiamen.

Freshly-singed battlegrounds effusing with the stench of the dead. Forbidden lands that will be excised from the memory of history. What better place than the realms of shadow then, for such an army?</text>
<text id="5280100">Armor as dark as shadow, worn by vulgar militiamen.

Freshly-singed battlegrounds effusing with the stench of the dead. Forbidden lands that will be excised from the memory of history. What better place than the realms of shadow then, for such an army?</text>
<text id="5280200">Gauntlets as dark as shadow, worn by vulgar militiamen.

Freshly-singed battlegrounds effusing with the stench of the dead. Forbidden lands that will be excised from the memory of history. What better place than the realms of shadow then, for such an army?</text>
<text id="5280300">Greaves as dark as shadow, worn by vulgar militiamen.

Freshly-singed battlegrounds effusing with the stench of the dead. Forbidden lands that will be excised from the memory of history. What better place than the realms of shadow then, for such an army?</text>
<text id="5290000">Ritual headwear in the form of a divine beast's head, used to perform the lion dance. Worn by the very finest of the sculpted keepers. Alas, it no longer responds to the old woman's earnest prayer.

Divine invocation heightens intensity of the storm alongside strength and dexterity, but reduces the restorative effect of drinking from a flask of sacred tears.

Focus is also troubled by wearing this headwear.</text>
<text id="5300000">St. Trina's life withered and fell, as fleeting as the seasons. At her last, she left a single water lily.

Slightly boosts max FP.

Despite the velvety-purple hue, the flower is in no way poisonous—it merely blooms in quietude.</text>
<text id="5310000">Helm worn by Devonia, longest-serving of the Crucible Knights.

Holds the power of the crucible of life, the primordial form of the Erdtree. Strengthens Aspects of the Crucible incantations.

It is said Devonia quested in search of the Crucible's origin, and departed from the lands of the Erdtree alone.</text>
<text id="5320000">A greatjar which fits comfortably over the head when upturned. Attire of the shamans who perform their worship at gaols.

Increases the power of thrown pots of all sizes.

They offer their prayers to the innards of the greatjars, such that they might be reborn one day into sainthood. This is the cycle of death and rebirth, taken into the hands of mortal men.</text>
<text id="5330000">Head covering made from the largely unaltered head of an impish golem.

Resembling a lion in appearance, life force faintly clings to it.</text>
</entries>
</fmg>